Indicates that Docker couldn't pull a Docker image from Amazon ECR,
OK,
the specific error is a 4 or 3 forbidden response which
usually points to an issue with permissions or access rights.
OK,
that's what we thought,
which is ***.
Uh-huh.
Since repositories with ECR are private by default,
both you and Player A have set up private repositories
that no-one else can access until you give someone else
specific permissions.
Yeah,
*** what we've set up are private repositories,
my friends.
Do you see even in the left-hand navigation panel for Maximus,
it's images that highlight a thing is under the heading private registry.
***,
*** what's really happening here is it's *** private that no one else,
literally no one else can have access until we give it to them specifically.
And that's the reason why we can just openly paste the
links to our registries in the chat because actually we know
that
even if you have access to that link,
you can't actually get access to
the registry itself until we give you specific access.
***.
Let's take a screenshot,
*** we're gonna go back to our terminal.
And just take a screenshot of this error right here.
Nice.
And I'm gonna paste that into
a box here
and then move on to the next question.